Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXII is arranged in 11 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XXIII is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXII. TRANSPORTATION
  - Sub-Series 232-0. Transportation
    - General, 1959-1962 (Box 115, Folder 8)
      Jan. 1, 1959-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - General, 1954-1958 (Box 115, Folder 9)
      Oct. 1954-Dec. 31, 1958.
    - General, 1953-1954 (Box 115, Folder 10)
      April 16, 1953-Sept. 1954.
    - General, 1952-1953 (Box 115, Folder 11)
      1952-April 15, 1953.
    - General, 1950-1951 (Box 115, Folder 12)
      Nov. 1950-51.
    - General, 1950 (Box 115, Folder 13)
      March 16, 1950-Oct. 1950.
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 115, Folder 14)
      July 1949-March 15, 1950.
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 115, Folder 15)
      Aug. 1948-June 1949.
    - General, 1948 (Box 115, Folder 16)
      March 1948-July 1948.
    - General, 1947-1948 (Box 115, Folder 17)
      1947-Feb. 1948.
    - General, 1942-1946 (Box 115, Folder 18)
      Sept. 1942-46.
    - General, 1942 (Box 115, Folder 19)
      Jan. 1942-Aug. 1942.
    - General, 1940-1941 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - General, 1937-1940 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 232-1. Transportation
    - General Chairmen, 1921-1938 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 232-2. Transportation
    - Grand Lodge Officers and Employees, 1940 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Grand Lodge Officers and Employees, 1928-1937 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 232-3. Transportation
    - Employees, Railway Express Agency, 1944-1955 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Employees, Railway Express Agency, 1939-1943 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Employees, Railway Express Agency, 1932-1938 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Express Employees, 1929-1931 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - 232-3(b). Employees, Railway Express Agency on Pennsylvania Railroad, 1930-1944 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - 232-3(c). Employees, Railway Express Agency on Southern Railway (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 232-4. Transportation
    - Colored Employees, 1929 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 232-5. Transportation
    - Trans-Atlantic Ocean, 1931-1947 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 232-6. Transportation
    - Express General Chairmen, 1932-1947 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Express General Chairmen, 1931 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 232-7. Transportation
    - Express Employees, 1932-1933 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 232-8. Transportation
    - New York Central Employees, 125th St. Station, New York City, 1934 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 232-9. Transportation
    - Employees of Freight Forwarding Companies, 1934 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 232-10. Transportation
    - Employees of Eastern Steamship (S. S.) Lines, 1937-1940 (Box 116, Folder 17)
- Series XXIII. EMPLOYMENT - GRAND LODGE
  - Sub-Series 233-0. Employment Grand Lodge
    - Jan. 1, 1963-Dec. 31, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Organizers, H. S. Chapman, 1933-1935 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - Organizers (A. J. Dunn, Vice Grand President), 1934 (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Organizers, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - Organizers, 1941-1966 (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - Organizers, 1945-1965 (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - Organizers, 1935-1965 (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - Organizers, 1937-1964 (Box 116, Folder 25)
    - Organizers, 1961-1965 (Box 116, Folder 26)
    - Organizers, 1947-1964 (Box 116, Folder 27)
    - Organizers, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 28)
    - Organizers, 1953-1965 (Box 116, Folder 29)
    - Organizers, 1953-1961 (Box 116, Folder 30)
    - Organizers, 1961-1962 (Box 116, Folder 31)
    - Organizers, 1959-1962 (Box 116, Folder 32)
    - 1959-Dec. 31, 1962 (Box 116, Folder 33)
    - 1943-Dec. 31, 1958 (Box 116, Folder 34)
    - Organizers, 1947-1961 (Box 117, Folder 1)
      Sept. 1947-Dec. 31, 1961.
    - Organizers, Thos. E. Derrick -1931-35 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Organizers, 1928-1930 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Organizers (Hugh McTigue, Vice Grand President), 1933-1934 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Organizers (F. H. Hall, Vice Grand President), 1933-1934 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Organizers, 1931 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Organizers, 1922 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - General Representatives (not in folder, tied together), 1920-1922 (Box 117, Folder 8)